(Sheldon:)and finds out
I don't have an Uncle Harvey?
(Leonard:)The dealer doesn't care,
Kripke has no authority over us,
(Leonard:)and you being related
to a metal container
(Leonard:)would explain a lot.
(Leonard:)Help me hook this up.
(Sheldon:)Uh-oh.
What?
(Sheldon:)Well, did you see this sticker?
What is it?
(Sheldon:)It's partially torn off, but
the segment that remains reads:
“Property of”
and the letter “U.”
(Leonard:)It's probably USC or UCLA.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but what if it's
“Property of U.S. Government”?
(Sheldon:)There's a national helium
reserve in Amarillo, Texas.
(Sheldon:)If this was stolen from there,
(Sheldon:)we're accessories
to a federal crime.
(Leonard:)Let's not jump to conclusions.
A lot of things start with “U.”
(Sheldon:)That's true.
(Sheldon:)There's the U.S. Air Force,
U.S. Department of Defense,
U.S. Navy,
“you” and I
are going to jail.
(Leonard:)Listen, we can
do the experiment as planned
(Leonard:)and beat the Swedish team
to the punch,
(Leonard:)or we can kiss our dreams
good-bye because we were
(Leonard:)to afraid to break a few rules.
(Leonard:)Ma'am.